acmethemes.com 2019-11-30

# Privacy Policy - Acme Themes

### What Information Do We Collect ?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number.However, you may visit our site anonymously.

### What Do We Use Your Information For ?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
• To personalize your experience. Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.  
• To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

• To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### Do We Use Cookies ?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

### Do We Disclose Any Information To Outside Parties ?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third Party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions ](http://www.acmethemes.com/terms-and-conditions/)section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

### Changes To Our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

Feel free to [contact us](http://www.acmethemes.com/contact/) if you have any questions to this website and our themes.
